Privacy Policy | Lover App Inc                     

top of page

Meet The Team

Learn

Dr. Britney Blair

Clinical Psychologist

Clinical Psychologist

Clinical Psychologist

Clinical Psychologist

Clinical Psychologist

Meet The Team

Learn

#### Privacy Policy

​

Updated as of: January 12, 2022

​

This Privacy Policy describes how Lover App, Inc., and our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively "Lover App," "we", “us” or "our") handle personal information that we collect through our websites  (collectively, the “Site”), our mobile application (the “App”), through social media, in connection with our marketing activities and through other activities described in this Privacy Policy (collectively the “Service”).

​

#### Table of Contents  

Information you provide to us. Personal information you may provide to us through the Service or otherwise includes:

Automatic data collection. We, our service providers, and our business partners may automatically log information about you, your computer or mobile device, and your activity over time on our sites and other sites and online services, such as:

How we use your personal information

Service delivery. We use your personal information to:

Research and development. We may use your personal information for research and development purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and our business. As part of these activities, we may use this data and share it with secure third parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze and improve the service and promote our business. There is absolutely no risk of your identity or use of Lover being made public. We only work with recognized and secure third parties, who have themselves passed all data security requirements.

Marketing and advertising.  We and our third-party advertising partners may collect and use your personal information for marketing and advertising purposes:

​

* Direct marketing. We may send you Lover App-related direct marketing communications as permitted by law, including by email.  You may opt-out of our marketing communications as described in the Opt-out of marketing section below.  

* Interest-based advertising.  We may contract with third-party advertising companies and social media companies to display ads on our Service and other sites. These companies may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about you (including the device data, online activity data and/or geolocation data described above) over time across our Service and other sites and services or your interaction with our emails, and use that information to serve ads that they think will interest you. You can learn more about your choices for limiting interest-based advertising in the Your choices section of our Cookie Notice.

​

Compliance and protection. We may use your personal information to:

* comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities;
    
* protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims);
    
* audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements and internal policies;
    
* enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Service; and
    
* prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.

​

How we share your personal information

Your choices

Access, update, or delete your information. If you have registered for an account with us, you may review, update, or delete certain account information by logging into the account.

Opt-out of marketing communications.  You may opt out of marketing-related emails by following the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email, or by contacting us.  You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails.

Privacy settings and location data.  Users of our App can disable our access to their device’s precise geolocation in their mobile device settings.

Cookies. For information about cookies employed by the Service and how to control them, see our Cookie Notice.

Do Not Track.  Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit.  We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals.  To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

Declining to provide information. We need to collect personal information to provide certain services. If you do not provide the information requested, we may not be able to provide those services.

Retention. We generally retain personal information to fulfill the purposes for which we collected it, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, to establish or defend legal claims, or for fraud prevention purposes.  To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we may consider factors such as the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which we process your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

When we no longer require the personal information we have collected about you, we may either delete it, anonymize it, or isolate it from further processing.

Other sites and services

The Service may contain links to websites, mobile applications, and other online services operated by third parties.  These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party.  In addition, our content may be included on web pages or in mobile applications or other online services that are not associated with us. We do not control websites, mobile applications or online services operated by third parties, and we are not responsible for their actions.

Security

We employ a number of technical, organizational and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information we collect.  However, security risk is inherent in all internet and information technologies and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information.

International data transfer

We are headquartered in the United States and may use service providers that operate in other countries. Your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other locations where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your state, province, or country.

Children

The Service is not intended for use by children under 18 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 18 without the consent of the child’s parent or guardian as required by law, we will delete it.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the date of this Privacy Policy and posting it on the Service. If required by law we will also provide notification of changes in another way that we believe is reasonably likely to reach you, such as via email or another manner through the Service.  Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting the modified version (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting). In all cases, your continued use of the Service after the effective date of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

How to contact us  
Your California privacy rights. As a California resident, you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases we may decline your request as permitted by law.

* Right to information, access and deletion. You may submit requests to exercise your right to information, access or deletion by:
    
    * emailing [support@lover.io](mailto:support@lover.io)

​

* Right to opt-out of the “sale” of your Personal Information.  Like many companies, we use services that help deliver interest-based ads to you, and have done so during the past 12 months.  Our use of some of these services may be classified under California law as a “sale” of your Personal Information to the advertising partners that provide the services because they collect information from our users (e.g., device data and online activity data) to help them serve ads more likely to interest you.  Information about how you can opt-out of use of your information for interest-based advertising is described in the “Your Choices” section in the Cookie Notice.

​

Personal information that we collect, use and disclose

* relying on our own or someone else's legitimate interests to process your personal information, unless  we can demonstrate compelling legal grounds for the processing; or  

* processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes.

​

Your choices

Changes

Questions

​

#### Personal information we collect

#### ​

Information you provide to us. Personal information you may provide to us through the Service or otherwise includes:

​

* Contact data, such as your first and last name and email address.
    
* Profile data, such as your username and password that you set to establish an online account with us, age range, gender, sexual orientation, personal relationship status, and sexual and non-sexual interests and preferences.
    
* Communications that we exchange with you, including meetings with coaches and when you contact us with questions, feedback, or otherwise.
    
* Payments and transactional data needed to complete your orders on or through the Service (including name, credit card information, bank account number, billing information), and your purchase history.
    
* Marketing data, such as your preferences for receiving communications about our products, services, activities, and publications, and details about how you engage with our communications.
    
* Other information that we may collect which is not specifically listed here, which we will use as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection.

​

Automatic data collection.  We, our service providers, and our business partners may automatically log information about you, your computer or mobile device, and your activity over time on our sites and other sites and online services, such as:

​

* Device data, such as your computer or mobile device operating system type and version number, manufacturer and model, browser type, screen resolution, IP address, unique identifiers, the website you visited before browsing to our website, and general location information such as city, state or geographic area.
    
* Online activity data, such as pages or screens you viewed, other Lover App users with whom you have shared content through the Service, how long you spent on a page or screen, navigation paths between pages or screens, information about your activity on a page or screen, access times, and duration of access.
    
* Precise geolocation data, when you authorize our mobile application to access your device’s location.

​

Cookies. Some of our automatic data collection is facilitated by cookies and similar technologies.  For more information, see our Cookie Notice.

​

#### How we use your personal information

#### ​

We use your personal information for the following purposes or as otherwise described at the time we collect it:

​

Service delivery. We use your personal information to:

​

* provide, operate and improve the Service and our business;
    
* establish and maintain your user profile on the Service;
    
* communicate with you about the Service, including by sending announcements, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
    
* understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience with the Service and our communications; and
    
* provide support for the Service, respond to your requests, questions and feedback.

​

Research and development. We may use your personal information for research and development purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and our business.  As part of these activities, we may create aggregated, de-identified or other anonymous data from personal information we collect.  We make personal information into anonymous data by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to you.  We may use this anonymous data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and promote our business.

​

Marketing and advertising. We and our third party advertising partners may collect and use your personal information for marketing and advertising purposes:

​

* Direct marketing. We may send you Lover App-related direct marketing communications as permitted by law, including by email. You may opt-out of our marketing communications as described in the Opt-out of marketing section below.
    
* Interest-based advertising. We may contract with third-party advertising companies and social media companies to display ads on our Service and other sites. These companies may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about you (including the device data, online activity data and/or geolocation data described above) over time across our Service and other sites and services or your interaction with our emails, and use that information to serve ads that they think will interest you. . You can learn more about your choices for limiting interest-based advertising in the Your choices section of our Cookie Notice.

​

Compliance and protection. We may use your personal information to:

​

* comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities;
    
* protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims);
    
* audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements and internal policies;
    
* enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Service; and
    
* prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.

​

#### How we share your personal information

#### ​

We may share your personal information with the following parties and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection:

​

Affiliates. Our corporate parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates, for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

​

Service providers. Companies and individuals that provide services on our behalf or help us operate the Service or our business (such as hosting, information technology, customer support, email delivery, and website analytics).

​

Advertising partners. Third party advertising companies that collect information about your activity on the Service and other online services to help us advertise our services, and/or use hashed customer lists that we share with them to deliver ads on their platforms to those customers and similar users.

​

Professional advisors. Professional advisors, such as lawyers, auditors, bankers and insurers, where necessary in the course of the professional services that they render to us.

​

Authorities and others. Law enforcement, government authorities, and private parties, as we believe in good faith to be necessary or appropriate for the compliance and protection purposes described above.

​

Business transferees. Relevant participants in business transactions (or potential transactions) involving a corporate divestiture, merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization, sale or other disposition of all or any portion of the business or assets of, or equity interests in, Lover App or our affiliates (including, in connection with a bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

​

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties on or through our Service, that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.

​

#### Your choices

#### ​

You have the following choices with respect to your personal information.

​

Access, update, or delete your information. If you have registered for an account with us, you may review, update, or delete certain account information by logging into the account.

​

Opt-out of marketing communications. You may opt out of marketing-related emails by following the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email, or by contacting us.  You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails.

​

Privacy settings and location data. Users of our App can disable our access to their device’s precise geolocation in their mobile device settings.

​

Cookies. For information about cookies employed by the Service and how to control them, see our Cookie Notice.

​

Do Not Track. Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit.  We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals.  To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

​

Declining to provide information. We need to collect personal information to provide certain services.  If you do not provide the information requested, we may not be able to provide those services.

​

Retention. We generally retain personal information to fulfill the purposes for which we collected it, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, to establish or defend legal claims, or for fraud prevention purposes.  To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we may consider factors such as the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which we process your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

​

When we no longer require the personal information we have collected about you, we may either delete it, anonymize it, or isolate it from further processing.

#### Other sites and services

#### ​

The Service may contain links to websites, mobile applications, and other online services operated by third parties. These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party. In addition, our content may be included on web pages or in mobile applications or other online services that are not associated with us. We do not control websites, mobile applications or online services operated by third parties, and we are not responsible for their actions.

​

#### Security

We employ a number of technical, organizational and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information we collect. However, security risk is inherent in all internet and information technologies and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information.

​

#### International data transfer

We are headquartered in the United States and may use service providers that operate in other countries. Your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other locations where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your state, province, or country.

​

#### Children

The Service is not intended for use by children under 18 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 18 without the consent of the child’s parent or guardian as required by law, we will delete it.

​

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the date of this Privacy Policy and posting it on the Service. If required by law we will also provide notification of changes in another way that we believe is reasonably likely to reach you, such as via email or another manner through the Service.  Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting the modified version (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting). In all cases, your continued use of the Service after the effective date of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

​

#### How to contact us

You can reach us by email at [support@lover.io](mailto:support@lover.io)

#### Information for California residents

Scope. This section applies only to the extent we qualify as a “business” as defined under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”). It described how we collect, use and share the Personal Information of California residents and their rights with respect to their Personal Information. For purposes of this section, “Personal Information” has the meaning given in the CCPA but does not include information exempted from the scope of the CCPA.  Additionally, this section does not apply to information we collect from you in the course of communicating with you in your capacity as an employee, controlling owner, director, officer or contractor of an organization (i.e., company, partnership, sole proprietorship, non-profit or government agency) in the context of performing due diligence on, or providing or receiving products or services to or from, that organization. In some cases we may provide a different privacy notice to certain categories of California residents, such as job applicants, in which case that notice will apply instead of this section. 

Your California privacy rights. As a California resident, you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases we may decline your request as permitted by law.

* Information. You can request the following information about how we have collected and used your Personal Information during the past 12 months:
    
    * The categories of Personal Information that we have collected.
        
    * The categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information.
        
    * The business or commercial purpose for collecting and/or selling Personal Information.
        
    * The categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information.
        
    * The categories of Personal Information that we sold or disclosed for a business purpose.
        
    * The categories of third parties to whom the Personal Information was sold or disclosed for a business purpose.  

* Access. You can request a copy of the Personal Information that we have collected about you during the past 12 months.   

* Deletion. You can ask us to delete the Personal Information that we have collected from you.  

* Opt-out of sales. If we sell your Personal Information, you can opt-out.  

* Nondiscrimination. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discrimination as prohibited by the CCPA.  

You may submit requests to exercise your California privacy rights described above as follows:

​

* Right to information, access and deletion. You may submit requests to exercise your right to information, access or deletion by:
    
    * emailing [](mailto:support@lover.io)[support@lover.io](mailto:support@lover.io)  

* Right to opt-out of the “sale” of your Personal Information.  Like many companies, we use services that help deliver interest-based ads to you, and have done so during the past 12 months.  Our use of some of these services may be classified under California law as a “sale” of your Personal Information to the advertising partners that provide the services because they collect information from our users (e.g., device data and online activity data) to help them serve ads more likely to interest you.  Information about how you can opt-out of use of your information for interest-based advertising is described in the “Your Choices” section in the Cookie Notice. 

​​

We will need to verify your identity to process your information, access and deletion requests and reserve the right to confirm your California residency.  Authentication into your Lover App account, government identification or other information may be required.  Your authorized agent may make a request on your behalf upon our verification of the agent’s identity and our receipt of a copy of a valid power of attorney given to your authorized agent pursuant to California Probate Code Sections 4000-4465.  If you have not provided your agent with such a power of attorney, you must provide your agent with written and signed permission to exercise your CCPA rights on your behalf, provide the information we request to verify your identity, and provide us with written confirmation that you have given the authorized agent permission to submit the request. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.

​

Personal information that we collect, use and disclose

​

The chart below describes the Personal Information we collect by reference to the categories of Personal Information specified in the CCPA, and describes our practices currently and during the 12 months preceding the effective date of this Privacy Policy. Information you voluntarily provide to us, such as in free-form webforms, may contain other categories of personal information not described below.

| Statutory category of personal information (PI) (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.140) | PI we collect in this category (See “Personal information we collect” above for description) | Source of PI | Business/ commercial purpose for collection | Categories of third parties to whom we “disclose” PI for a business purpose | Categories of third parties to whom we “sell” PI |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers | • Contact data • Profile data • Data about others | • You • Third party sources | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |
| Commercial Information | • Profile data • Payment & transactional data • Marketing data • Online activity data | • You • Third party sources • Automatic collection | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |
| Financial Information | • Payment & transactional data | • You | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | None |
| Online Identifiers | • Profile data • Device data | • You • Automatic collection | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |
| Internet or Network Information | • Marketing data • Device data • Online activity data | • Automatic collection | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |
| Geolocation Data | • Device data • Precise geolocation data | • Automatic collection | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |
| Inferences | May be derived from your: • Payment & transactional data • Activity data • Marketing data • Device data • Online activity data | N/A | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |
| Protected Classification Characteristics | • Age • Sex • Sexual Orientation | • You | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |
| Personal information as defined in the California customer records law | • Information about conditions relating to sexuality | • You | • Service delivery • Research & development • Marketing & advertising • Compliance & protection | • Affiliates • Advertising partners • Professional advisors • Authorities and others • Business transferees | • Advertising partners (to facilitate online advertising) |

#### Cookie Notice

This Cookie Notice explains how Lover App, Inc. (“Lover App”, “we”, “us” or “our”) uses cookies and similar technologies in connection with 

* the [](http://www.lover.io/)[www.lover.io](http://www.lover.io/) website and any other website that we own or control and which posts or links to this Cookie Notice (collectively, the “Sites”); and
    
* our mobile app (“App”).

​

What are cookies?

Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website.  Cookies serve different purposes, like helping us understand how a site is being used, letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences and generally improving your browsing experience.

Our Sites may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer or mobile device until you delete them).

We use two broad categories of cookies: (1) first party cookies, served directly by us to your computer or mobile device, which we use to recognize your computer or mobile device when it revisits our Sites; and (2) third party cookies, which are served by service providers or business partners on our Sites, and can be used by these parties to recognize your computer or mobile device when it visits other websites. Third party cookies can be used for a variety of purposes, including site analytics, advertising and social media features.

What types of cookies and similar tracking technologies does Lover App use on the Sites and App?

On the Sites and App, we use cookies and other tracking technologies in the following categories described in the table below.

​

| Type | Who serves the cookies (link to privacy policy/site) | How to control them |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Advertising These cookies or SDKs are used by advertising companies to collect information about how you use our Sites and other websites over time. These companies use this information to show you ads they believe will be relevant to you within our services and elsewhere, and to measure how the ads perform. | https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation | See ‘your choices’ below. |
| Analytics These cookies or SDKs help us understand how our services is performing and being used. These cookies may work with web beacons included in emails we send to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. | AppsFlyer https://www.appsflyer.com/privacy-policy/ Mixpanel https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/ Google Analytics https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites | See ‘your choices’ below. |
| Essential These cookies or SDKs are necessary to allow the technical operation of our services (e.g., they enable you to move around on a website and to use its features). | FireBase https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy | See ‘your choices’ below. |
| Functionality / performance Enhance the performance and functionality of our services. | Intercom https://www.intercom.com/legal/privacy SendBird https://sendbird.com/privacy TimeKit https://help.timekit.io/en/articles/1345997-global-privacy-policy | See ‘your choices’ below. |

Page 1 of 2

Other technologies

In addition to cookies, our Sites may use other technologies, such as Flash technology to pixel tags to collect information automatically.

Browser Web Storage

We may use browser web storage (including via HTML5), also known as locally stored objects (“LSOs”), for similar purposes as cookies. Browser web storage enables the storage of a larger amount of data than cookies. Your web browser may provide functionality to clear your browser web storage.

Flash Technology

We may use Flash cookies (which are also known as Flash Local Shared Object (“Flash LSOs”)) on our Sites to collect and store information about your use of our Sites. Unlike other cookies, Flash cookies cannot be removed or rejected via your browser settings. If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer or mobile device, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the Website Storage Settings Panel. You can also control Flash LSOs by going to the Global Storage Settings Panel and following the instructions. Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with our Sites.

Web Beacons

We may also use web beacons (which are also known as pixel tags and clear GIFs) on our Sites and in our HTML formatted emails to track the actions of users on our Sites and interactions with our emails. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device by a website, pixel tags are embedded invisibly on webpages or within HTML formatted emails. Pixel tags are used to demonstrate that a webpage was accessed or that certain content was viewed, typically to measure the success of our marketing campaigns or engagement with our emails and to compile statistics about usage of the Sites, so that we can manage our content more effectively.

Mobile Application Software Development Kits (SDKs)

We may use third-party software development kits (“SDKs”) in our mobile applications. A SDK is third-party computer code that may be used for a variety of purposes, including to provide us with analytics regarding the use of our mobile applications, to integrate with social media, add features or functionality to our app, or to facilitate online advertising. SDKs may enable third parties to collect information directly via our App.

Your choices

Your options for controlling what information cookies and similar technologies collect about you include:

​

* Blocking cookies in your browser. Most browsers let you remove or reject cookies.  To do this, follow the instructions in your browser settings.  Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings.  Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, the Sites may not work properly.  For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). If you do not accept our cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of our Sites. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer or mobile device and you may need to log in every time you visit our Sites.  

* Third party opt-out option. You can opt-out of interest-based advertising through some of the third parties listed in the chart above by using the corresponding third party opt-out tool provided in the chart.   

* Industry association opt-outs.  You may opt out of receiving interest-based advertising on websites through members of the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or the Digital Advertising Alliance by clicking [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices), or by clicking [here](http://www.edaa.eu/) if you are in Europe.  You may opt out of receiving targeted advertising in mobile apps through participating members of the Digital Advertising Alliance by installing the AppChoices mobile app, available [here](https://www.youradchoices.com/appchoices), and selecting the user’s choices. Please note that we also may work with companies that offer their own opt-out mechanisms and may not participate in the opt-out mechanisms linked above.  

* Blocking advertising ID use in your mobile settings. Your mobile device settings may provide functionality to limit use of the advertising ID associated with your mobile device for interest-based advertising purposes.

​

For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).  If you do not accept our cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of our Sites. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer or mobile device and you may need to log in every time you visit our Sites.

If you choose to opt-out of targeted advertisements, you will still see advertisements online but they may not be relevant to you. Even if you do choose to opt out, not all companies that serve online behavioral advertising are included in this list, and so you may still receive some cookies and tailored advertisements from companies that are not listed.

For more information about how we collect, use and share your information, see our [Privacy Policy](https://www.lover.io/privacy-policy).

Changes

Information about the cookies we use may be updated from time to time, so please check back on a regular basis for any changes.

Questions

If you have any questions about this Cookie Notice, please contact us by email at [support@lover.io](mailto:support@lover.io).

Last modified: January 12 2022.

​

Contact Us

bottom of page
